tdiclub.com 2017-05-20

# Privacy Statement

###    
Privacy Statement

TDIClub (TDIClub Online Ltd.) is committed to protecting the privacy of individuals. 

**How Information is Collected and Used** The Authority collects personal information that is voluntarily provided by you when using certain portions of this website; such as 'contact us', 'e-commerce' or 'reservations'. This information is collected for the purpose in which it was given; respond to your inquiry, ship your product, or make your reservation. By providing us with your personal information, you consent to the use of your personal information in accordance with this privacy statement. The Authority will not disclose any personal information to any third party, except as required by law and as is necessary to fulfill your request. 

**Cookies and Log Files** Cookies are data files sent to your browser and stored on your hard-drive when you visit certain websites.  These are used in the forums section of the website.  If you want to remove these cookies from the site, click clearing all cookies set on this message board by clicking http://forums.tdiclub.com/cgi-bin/ultimatebb.cgi?ubb=clearcookies.  TDIClub also has log files, which records the IP address of your computer. TDIClub uses log files to track the number of hits to its website. 

**Storage of and Access to Personal Information** Information posted in the forums may be retained on the website indefinitely.  The same applies to emails sent to the administrator or moderators, but is not guaranteed.  You can set how much personal information you want to be available to others, but is accessible by administrators of TDIClub.  This information will not be sold or traded. 

**Security** TDIClub does not represent, warrant or guarantee that personal information is protected from loss or misuse, including misuse of third parties, nor the accuracy of the information provided. TDIClub has taken security measures with respect to the storage of personal information in the attempt to maintain the safety of such information. 

**Links** This website contains links to third party sites. TDIClub is not responsible for the collection of personal information nor the privacy of such information on third party sites. 

If you have any questions or concerns with respect to this privacy statement, please send an email through [contact us](http://www.tdiclub.com/email). 

TDIClub reserves the right to change this privacy statement at any time. Such changes will be posted on this page.

Last update: May 29, 2007
